[Music]
PanAm myself as a country has gone into
a free trade agreement and a whole whole
Commission is actually going into a
digitized patient I'll file concept so
what happened is that they're
encouraging cashless payment so with the
cow encouragement people to pay cashless
more and more people open up bank
account so customer based on thank you
Chris tremendously second a lot of banks
here the experience happening of the
credit growth on the stick panel that
Nam so we're tightening on that credit
growth they need to find new source of
revenue and what is better than a
risk-free kind of fee income from banker
bank insurance business so long bangs up
keeping focus on language business as
well to an entity as a whole consumer
prefer one sub solution going to the
bank that can allow them to fulfill most
of their financial services needs
[Music]
the beach channel itself has got its own
unique proposition offers its own daily
opposition to various segments of the
customer and various channel actually
cater to various segments of the
customer as well Manulife is the
multi-channel approach company so to us
we embrace and believe that we need to
give customer choice and I will respect
us on the decision this is how we manage
the channel hopefully let the customer
have a choice and we respect their
decision
[Music]
I think the key is that we must first
understand the value and culture of our
partner after after sending them we need
to get full party insurer as far as
banking self to make poor committed in
this piece of business once the seed
investment and culture is committed
driving this piece of business we then
look into it created or the difference
type of PV operation product offering
system as well as people support to both
organization and with this style
integration they actually works well
towards a very sustainable sustainable
kind of partnership from the top they
may have a lot belief they may be
committed but also it boils down to
execution QB o what we realize that a
lot of people may have the desire may be
committed but when it comes to execution
and honest thing they do not have the
ability to escape out so one of the
fundamental in actually fostering a good
partnership is that we must be able to
have the execution capital and also with
a collaboration myself wanting to work
closely with a panel in a win-win
situation
[Music]
execution execution capability you need
to find the right people with the right
talent from the right knowledge in the
toast necessary area so for example we
need to integrate a product you can bank
itself really a person who understand
not just insurance product but also
understand the various customer segments
of the banking missile so a key is
actually we need to find a pattern we
need the people we don't know how to do
it so
oh boy sound execution oh boy sound
finding the right what we do we feed it
make sure a GP assess into that the bank
system itself locks in power here are 15
years so thanks for 15 years is up i
what you see over after then it depends
a lot on how Bhupati
see the relationship and how they view
that can continue for long term
sustainable client relationship again
subsequently future moving on it the
valuation can be done again and the
valuation will be done based on whether
to dig are they able to derive value
from the upfront fee again from the next
15 years I will believe that a lot of
time when a partnership has been locking
fairly good close for 15 years judges of
renewing or next 15 years or beyond
their time and of course how much PP
really depends on evaluation back then
and how much value for that we can
provide
[Music]
the business potential for example if I
were to look at that man itself the
customer based the bank keep increasing
and they've been increasing
exponentially and come to me the renewal
and all these will be done into
consideration like oh this sub base that
hasn't gone up by two times three times
then but it's a kind of value that can
get this new customer base again and all
this so market like like that none where
there are only 25% and how the banking
account
currently and it's growing quite
exponentially I do see that many Libyans
down the loop when it comes to renewal
with a bigger customer beings the value
that we can work together if a partner
or public would come up with that one up
so that the valuation would be very
different for probably many years back
OPP whatever business and he goes into
there's always at least whether is a
panel shape or another piece whatever
business that we go see you the key
thing is that be aware of the risk and
proactively mitigate the risk so that
chances of it happening is high and then
falls down to what I just mentioned the
my set in terms of the senior management
committed to working together in grim
institution and the execution capability
that's my view of inertia description
[Music]